[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "letter": "A",
    "question": "A common fruit",
    "answer": "apple",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "letter": "B",
    "question": "A buzzing insect",
    "answer": "bee",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "letter": "C",
    "question": "Used to describe something cold",
    "answer": "chilly",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "letter": "D",
    "question": "A man's title",
    "answer": "doctor",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "letter": "E",
    "question": "A large mammal with big ears",
    "answer": "elephant",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "letter": "F",
    "question": "Opposite of success",
    "answer": "failure",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "letter": "G",
    "question": "Used to measure weight",
    "answer": "gram",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "letter": "H",
    "question": "Frozen water",
    "answer": "hail",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "letter": "I",
    "question": "Opposite of out",
    "answer": "in",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "letter": "J",
    "question": "Used to describe a court worker",
    "answer": "judge",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "letter": "K",
    "question": "A baby cat",
    "answer": "kitten",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "letter": "L",
    "question": "What you do when you find something funny",
    "answer": "laugh",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "letter": "M",
    "question": "Opposite of female",
    "answer": "male",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "letter": "N",
    "question": "A compass direction",
    "answer": "north",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "letter": "O",
    "question": "Round and often worn on fingers",
    "answer": "opal",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "letter": "P",
    "question": "A place where you store things",
    "answer": "pantry",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "letter": "Q",
    "question": "A line of people",
    "answer": "queue",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "letter": "R",
    "question": "A color and also a fruit",
    "answer": "raspberry",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "letter": "S",
    "question": "Used to describe something sharp",
    "answer": "spike",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "letter": "T",
    "question": "Hot beverage",
    "answer": "tea",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "letter": "U",
    "question": "Opposite of down",
    "answer": "up",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "letter": "V",
    "question": "A type of car",
    "answer": "van",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "letter": "W",
    "question": "Falling water from the sky",
    "answer": "water",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "letter": "X",
    "question": "Used to describe something unknown",
    "answer": "x-factor",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "letter": "Y",
    "question": "Color between green and orange",
    "answer": "yellow",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "letter": "Z",
    "question": "A black and white striped animal",
    "answer": "zebra",
    "status": "NOT_STARTED"
  }
]
